<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MicroBoss</string>
    <string name="about_us">
        OUR VISION\n\n

        “Building human capacity
to enhance our global team
in evolving advancement through creative,
innovative and insightful development of new and efficient technologies,
strategies and infrastructure to provide hybrid solutions to varying client needs for human endeavor”.\n\n
        \nMISSION\n\n

“To provide Total IT Solutions across Africa and the International community, innovate cutting-edge and pragmatic solutions that deliver great value to the world, as we develop competent and accomplished professionals and expertise to support such services, and ensure that our client\'s experience is worry-free”.\n\n

        \nOUR CORE VALUES\n\n
        MicroBoss is a highly ethical company, which does business with speed, dedication, efficiency, proficiency and Integrity, conducting itself with high professional integrity and being socially responsible to its communities.
MicroBoss offer professional services delivered by highly qualified staff with extensive experience in prompt service delivery, development and management techniques to meet a wide variety of needs.
MicroBoss applies very detailed and strict project management standards and methodology during solution implementation. Our staff applies time proven, disciplined methodology to help clients implement Business Intelligence solutions quickly to achieve rapid measurable success. Our focus is to implement best practices with the ability to make every project phase fully transparent, cost effective and on schedule.\n\n

        \n#1 ICT SOLUTION PROVIDER IN AFRICA.\n\n

        MicroBoss Technologies is a premier technology solutions provider and value-added service company in Africa with focus on System Integration, Energy Services, Security Solutions, Control Automation, Customer Engagement Solutions, Collaborative Portals, Technology integration and Professional development. Our services include delivering high quality and cost- effective business automation products and solutions i.e EDMS, ERP, Document Digitization, Process Automation, Software and Web Applications for mid-sized and large-scale companies and global organizations.
We are a fast-paced global Information Technology Consulting firm with the aim to be a leading management and technology services organization and to satisfy the most advanced and demanding client needs in the African Sub-Region. We bring to the market, a combined strength that is a compelling proposition for businesses including - deep local expertise and presence aligned with a global footprint and resource bank, committed as a team to growing Nigeria\'s aspirations throughpeople,passionand technology.
\n\nWe build and deliver Enterprise grade solutions for a variety of corporate and business needs, deploying same over large territories or simple campus sites. SAP, SharePoint, Microsoft Dynamics to mention a few are some solutions we have great expertise working with. We equally offer mobile and web services to support video, voice, educational and entertainment content delivery globally to the satisfaction of our clients and customers, by combining our expertise in application technologies and service delivery with our network of relationship with telecom operators, advertising agencies, media organizations and other content providers. This enables us to develop innovative marketing, banking, entertainment, communications and other various business solutions to meet up with today\'s technological demand.
\n\nWe offer services to suit all types of customers ranging from those designed for organizations that are implementing performance management for the first time, to a knowledge transfer model for those who want to take greater immediate ownership of their solution. In each case, MicroBoss can help you utilize our multi-stage service, offering best practices process for implementation of customized scalable development amongst otherkeyprocesses.We also provide a product independent service which allows us to use tools that will suit the needs of the client and leverage on the clients existing infrastructure to
provide the optimal mix of services required based on their level of experience, availability of IT support and our clients budget. MicroBoss Technologies Limited was established in 2010 and registered in accordance with the Corporate Affairs Commission in Nigeria and has since being doing businesses with Small and medium businesses as well as Enterprise Organizations. Our operational headquarters is in Abuja-Nigeria.
\n\nWe are recognized partners of leading enterprise solution companies MicroSoft and SAP as well as technology providers of Dell/EMC and Intel. Our consultants and staff have the necessary technical, architectural, and project management skills to successfully implement any project we accept. We also can often accelerate the rate of implementation by utilizing prior project success and experience gained through similar engagements.\n\n\nFind out more by contacting us at;\nhello@microboss.org\nwww.microboss.org</string>
    <string name="terms_policy">PRIVACY POLICY\n\n This document is protected under the copyright laws of Nigeria and other countries as an unpublished work. This document contains information that is proprietary and confidential to MicroBoss Technologies Limited and shall not be disclosed outside, duplicated or used in whole or in part for any purpose other than to evaluate the suitability of MicroBoss to carry out work detailed within. Any use or disclosure in whole or in part of this information without the express written permission of MicroBoss Technologies Ltd is prohibited.
If a contract is awarded to MicroBoss Technologies Limited, as a result of, or in connection with, the submission of this document, any right to duplicate, use, or disclose the data will be to the extent provided in the resulting agreement. Recipient agrees that no license is being granted by MicroBoss Technologies Ltd and further agrees that all confidential and or proprietary information contained in this document shall remain the sole property of MicroBoss Technologies Ltd
All transactions are subject to the appropriate MicroBoss Technologies Standard Terms and Conditions.

\n\n
MICROBOSS TECHNOLOGIES LTD. SERVICE LEVEL AGREEMENT OVERVIEW.
MICROBOSS TECHNOLOGIES PRIVACY POLICY \nEffective Date: February 1, 2020\n
Please see the Glossary for definitions and explanations of capitalized terms used in this Privacy Policy.\n\nRespect for the privacy of your personal and other information is extremely important to us @ MicroBoss. When you use our Site(s), our App, Platform or otherwise communicate with us (e.g. via email) you will provide, and MicroBoss will collect, certain information, some of which can be used to personally identify and/or locate you (“Personal Information”). This Privacy Policy describes and is intended to help you understand what that Personal Information comprises, how MicroBoss uses that Personal Information, and what safeguards are in place to protect that Personal Information. \n\n
By using this Site, the Platform and/or otherwise communicating with us, you agree to this Privacy Policy so Please read it. \n
MicroBoss complies with the Nigerian Data Protection Regulation regarding the collection, use, and retention of Personal Information transferred within and outside the country. If there is any conflict between the terms in this Privacy Policy and the Nigerian Data Protection Regulation, the MicroBoss Privacy Policy shall govern. \n\n
NOTICE. \n
We are providing this Privacy Policy to you to describe the ways we collect, use, transfer, store, secure and protect Personal Information, the ways you can exercise your rights to access and control your Personal Information, and the complaint and recourse methods available to you. \n\n
INFORMATION COLLECTED ON THE MICROBOSS SITE \n
When you use our platform at MicroBoss, create an account to use the Site (or someone, such as your organization’s administrator, creates an account on your behalf), use our Platform or otherwise communicate with us (e.g. via email), Personal Information will be collected by the Site or Platform. \n\n
The Personal Information collected is as follows: \n
•	Name \n
•	Business address \n
•	Telephone number \n
•	Business telephone number \n
•	Email address \n
•	Location Data \n
•	IP-address and other online identifiers \n
•	Any customer testimonial you have given us consent to share on the Site \n

\n
•	Information you provide to the Site’s Interactive Areas. Note that any information that you post in an Interactive Area might be read, collected, and used by others who access it. You may take down any information you have added to the Interactive Areas at any time. \n
•	To request removal of your personal information from an Interactive Area, please contact us at team@MicroBoss.org \n
•	Information you provide via fillable forms or text boxes, such as training, webinars, or event registration. \n
•	Information regarding the device you are using, comprising the hardware model, operating system and version, unique device identifiers, network information, IP address, and/or Platform information when interacting with the Site or Platform. \n
•	Information about all your interactions with the Site or Platform (“Usage Data”) and how the Site or Platform is performing (“Analytics Data”). \n
•	Usage Data includes information regarding any interaction you have with the Site or Platform, such as which functionalities are used and the frequency of use (e.g., pages visited, actions taken, queries run, fields added, user accounts, account roles, and connected database types). \n
•	License checks including the number of users, roles, and database connections. \n
•	Analytics Data includes information gathered via our licensing management service, which sends data to MicroBoss concerning the performance of the Site or Platform. \n\n
•	If a MicroBoss customer uses the software to analyse personal data in their databases, MicroBoss will process the categories of personal data analysed, which may include special categories of data as determined by the customer, including without limitation factors specific to the individual’s physical, physiological, genetic,
mental, economic, cultural or social identity. \n
•	Information gathered through cookies, pixel tags, logs, or other similar technologies.
See “COOKIES AND RELATED TECHNOLOGIES” section below. \n\n
ADDITIONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THE MICROBOSS PLATFORM \n
When you use the Platform, create an account to use the Platform (or someone, such as your organization’s administrator, creates an account on your behalf), additional information about your use of the Platform is collected: \n
Unique identifier(s) we assign to users as part of monitoring user experience.
If you choose to log into the Platform using external directory systems or single sign-on services, these services enable you to share with us certain information to authenticate your identity and pre-populate certain forms on the Platform. Note that even if you subsequently stop using the services, we will retain the information you have shared with us, in accordance with this Privacy Policy. \n
Information contained in your organization’s MicroBoss database used with the Platform, to which we have access when we automatically back it up and possibly encrypt it for you. \n
As well as the processes described above, you may also choose: not to provide certain Personal Information when requested (e.g. via forms available on the Site); and/or to opt- out of the collection of certain Personal Information by us, by emailing us at admin@MicroBoss.org with the header: “Request to be provisioned for Manual Account Creation”. \n

\nSee also “COOKIES AND RELATED TECHNOLOGIES” section below for information about how information generated using these technologies is used.
MicroBoss also may collect information that does not identify or locate you personally, meaning business information such as SIC code, industry, number of employees, or sales funnel status. MicroBoss reserves the right to maintain, disclose, or otherwise use such information without limitation including aggregated data with other information to improve the Site, Platform and services offered by MicroBoss. \n\n
DATA INTEGRITY AND PURPOSE LIMITATION> THIS SECTION DESCRIBES THE WAYS WE USE AND STORE PERSONAL INFORMATION. \n
INFORMATION STORED BY MICROBOSS \n\
MicroBoss uses a read-only connection to access the minimum amount of data needed to answer your questions and only returns the relevant result set. Alternatively, customers can choose to give MicroBoss write-access to their database to take advantage of PDTs (persistent derived tables). This feature lets you define summary tables that MicroBoss will write on your behalf into your database, at a cadence of your choosing. \n
Accordingly, MicroBoss holds two types of Personal Information, in two ways: information about MicroBoss users, and the customer data necessary to answer MicroBoss users’ queries. \n
Information about MicroBoss users. This information about MicroBoss users includes end- user login/registration information for MicroBoss users as well as metadata about their usage. Metadata is used to facilitate product improvements, customer support and license auditing. Login information is controlled by customers directly as it is entered on their MicroBoss instance and they can delete their users’ (i.e. their employees’) information at any time. We retain basic user contact information to send product updates, relevant marketing, training and events based on the users’ communication preferences. \n
Customer data necessary to answer users’ queries. Once MicroBoss is connected to a customer database, the MicroBoss cache retains data from the customer’s database that is fetched in response to its users’ queries. This data may be encrypted and stored by MicroBoss. \n\n
HOW INFORMATION MAY BE USED BY THE MICROBOSS SITE \n
MicroBoss may use the Personal Information collected by the Site or Platform as follows: \n
•	To respond to your requests for information about our products, services, training
and events. \n
•	To provide product enablement and licensing, customer service and support. \n
•	To administer your account if you have registered on the Site or Platform, including
billing and payment. \n
•	To enable your access and use of the Site or Platform, and to enable you to
communicate, collaborate, and share information with those you designate. \n
•	To send you technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and
administrative messages. \n
•	To inform you about our products and services. \n
•	To apply information security policies and controls on the Site, including overall Site
integrity, identity management and account authentication. \n
•	For legal compliance, such as to enforce our legal rights, to comply in good faith with
applicable laws, and to protect users of the Site or Platform. \n
•	For other general business management and operations purposes, such as to
provide, operate, maintain, make modifications to protect and improve the Site or
Platform. \n
•	To send marketing, advertising, training or event materials to which you’ve agreed,
requested or subscribed. \n
•	For research and development to improve the MicroBoss product, Platform and
services. \n
•	For other purposes about which we notify you and, where relevant or required, give
you choice about the new purpose. \n\n
ADDITIONAL INFORMATION USED BY THE MICROBOSS PLATFORM \n
MicroBoss may use your Personal Information collected by the Platform as follows, depending upon the nature of the MicroBoss platform deployment: \n
•	To administer your Platform user account. \n
•	To enable your access and use of the Platform, and to enable you to communicate,
collaborate, and share information with those you designate. \n
•	To enable your access and use of Platform Integration and Application services. \n
•	To monitor your user experience on the Platform. \n
•	To enable MicroBoss to proactively help customers maintain the performance and
functionality of deployments of the Platform. \n
•	To enable MicroBoss to verify your license to use the Platform. \n\n
CHOICE, CONTROL AND ACCESS \n
This section describes the ways you can exercise your rights to access and control your Personal Information. \n\n
EMAIL COMMUNICATIONS PREFERENCES \n
MicroBoss respects your email communications and marketing preferences. If you prefer not to receive product release notes communications or promotional email messages (such as marketing, events, training) from MicroBoss, you can unsubscribe from MicroBoss’s email marketing list by following the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of each promotional email, going to our subscription centre, or contacting us at unsubscribe@MicroBoss.org with “UNSUBSCRIBE” in the subject line. Note: Please allow five (5) business days to be removed from all email communications. \n\n
ACCESSING, CORRECTING AND DELETING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION \n
Ensuring that Personal Information we hold about you is accurate and complete is important to us. If you would like to request access to, correct or delete the Personal Information, please send us an email at “admin@MicroBoss.org. We’ll verify these requests and respond to you in accordance with our legal obligations, which typically means forwarding your request to the licensed administrator (customer) of your MicroBoss account for review. \n\n
To request removal of your personal information from an Interactive Area, please contact us at unsubscribe@MicroBoss.org \n\n
MicroBoss customers create and remain in control of their data and data about user activities and reports. If you wish to delete a MicroBoss user’s account data, we have a process to permanently anonymize the info by data engineering, either self-serve or on request. If you would like MicroBoss to delete your customer data or MicroBoss user account detail, please send an email to team@MicroBoss.org. \n\n
ACCOUNTABILITY AND ONWARD TRANSFER \n
This section describes our accountability about the onward transfer of your Personal Information to third party service providers (suppliers), partners and across country borders. \n\n
INFORMATION SHARING \n
Except as listed below, MicroBoss will not share Personal Information with third parties unless you have consented to the disclosure.
Depending on how MicroBoss solutions are deployed by the customer, MicroBoss may share Personal Information with third-party service providers that need your information to provide the following operational or other support services to MicroBoss, the Site or Platform: \n\n
•	Data management. \n
•	Database hosting. \n
•	Integration services. \n
•	Professional services. \n
•	Information security, integrity, and identity and authentication services. \n
•	Email communications (e.g. operational, marketing, events, training). \n
•	Financial operations (e.g. licensing, billing). \n
•	Payments and payment card processing. \n
•	Shipping services. \n
•	Communication services (e.g enabling collaboration, conferencing or messaging). \n
•	Support services (e.g. providing customer service and support). \n
•	Cloud services (e.g. functioning of the Site or Platform). \n\n
The Site or Platform may contain links to a number of sites owned and operated by third parties that may offer useful information. The policies and procedures described in this Privacy Policy do not apply to those third-party sites. Please contact those third-party sites for information on their data collection, security, and distribution policies. \n\n
To ensure the confidentiality and security of your Personal Information, we ask service providers that handle Personal Information to sign a Data Protection Addendum. These service providers are restricted by contract from using your Personal Information in any way other than to provide services for MicroBoss. MicroBoss is accountable and has liability in cases of onward transfers to third party service providers. \n\n
MicroBoss does not share the information contained in your organization’s MicroBoss database and used with the MicroBoss Platform with the above third parties. \n\n
If you integrate a 3rd party service through a MicroBoss Action, Integration or Application Hub, or through Professional Services, you are choosing to share the information contained in your organization’s MicroBoss database with that 3rd party service. \n\n
MicroBoss may also provide your Personal Information to a third party if: \n
We believe that disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or lawful government request, including in connection with national security or law enforcement requirements. This may include disclosures: to respond to subpoenas or court orders; to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; or to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Service Agreement, or as otherwise required by law. In each case, we will make reasonable efforts to verify the validity of the request before disclosing your personal information where we deem it necessary. \n\n
•	To enforce our agreements, policies and Terms of Service. \n
•	To protect the security and integrity of the Site. \n
•	To respond to an emergency which we believe in good faith requires us to disclose information to assist in preventing serious bodily injury or death of any person. \n\n
MicroBoss may also share your Personal Information with our subsidiaries, affiliates, and partners, to facilitate our global operations and in accordance with applicable laws, our Service Agreement, Terms of Service or Contracts. We may also provide your Personal Information to a third party in connection with a merger, expansion or acquisition of MicroBoss or its subsidiary, either in part or in whole, or the assignment or other transfer of the Site. \n\n
You may choose to opt-out of allowing your Personal Information to be shared with certain third parties. To do so, please contact unsubscribe@MicroBoss.org with your request. We will do our best to respond in a timely manner and grant your request to the extent permitted by law. \n\n
INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER AND STORAGE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED \n
We primarily store information collected from you globally. By default, MicroBoss hosts in Nigeria, South Africa, the U.S. region, Canada, United Kingdom, Singapore and in Dubai, but at the customer’s request, we can host in various other regions, including within the EU, Asia and Latin America, which varies based on each unique customer circumstances. \n\n
To facilitate our global operations, we may transfer and access such personal information from around the world, including from other countries in which MicroBoss has operations. For customers who need to be hosted inside the EU, we host in London, Germany or Finland. Customers can also host their own MicroBoss instance on their own servers/network. We use applicable, approved information transfer mechanisms where required. \n\n
DATA SECURITY \n
MicroBoss has a dedicated Information Security Service responsible for security and data compliance across the organization. \n
MicroBoss protects the Personal Information it collects via the Site or Platform with reasonable and appropriate physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards. Most sections of the Site or Platform that collect sensitive Personal Information use industry-standard secure socket layer (TLS/SSL) encryption. To take advantage of TLS, your browser must support up-to-date encryption protection, as found in the latest versions of most common browsers, such as Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Google Chrome, and Safari. \n\n
COOKIES AND RELATED TECHNOLOGIES \n
Cookies are small data files that are placed on users’ devices to monitor how users interact with websites and other online services. Pixel tags, also called web beacons or single-pixel gifs, tag a graphic on a web page or in an email message that tracks pages viewed or email messages opened. Logs are continuous digital records of events and interactions that occur on a website. Cookies, pixel tags, and/or logs can be used to identify your IP address, browser type, domain name, and specific web pages through which you click and/or email messages you open. \n\n
OUR DETAILED COOKIE POLICY. \n
MicroBoss and our service providers may use cookies, pixel tags, and/or logs because they: \n\n
•	are essential for us to provide our Site or Platform to you. \n
•	help us optimize, personalize and/or otherwise improve your experience and/or the performance of the Site and our service and marketing-related communications with you; and \n
• enable advertising delivered to you to be more relevant. \n
Most web browsers allow you to erase cookies on your computer, block cookies from your computer, or notify you when a cookie is stored on your computer. If you choose to disable or otherwise block certain cookies, you may be unable to use, or experience decreased functionality with, parts of the Site. Your browser may also support functions to block or restrict pixel tags. \n\n
HOW WE RESPOND TO “DO NOT TRACK SIGNALS” \n
We track visitors to the Site over time (see “COOKIES AND RELATED TECHNOLOGIES” section above), We do not track visitors to the Site across third-party websites and therefore we do not respond to Do Not Track signals in these circumstances. \n\n
OUR ADVERTISEMENTS \n
MicroBoss’s third-party service providers serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. Some of these ads may be personalized for you based on information collected from your use of the Site. We do not share any of your Personal Information with the third-party service providers that serve ads on behalf of MicroBoss. \n\n
MINIMUM AGE \n
MicroBoss offers a suite of business services, not a consumer product. The Site or Platform is not directed to, nor intended to be used by, individuals under the age of 7, or the equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction. MicroBoss does not knowingly collect personal information from individuals under the age of 7, or the equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction. If you become aware that an individual under the age of 7, or the equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction, has provided us with personal
information, please contact us immediately at team@microboss.org If we become aware that an individual under the age of 7, or the equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction, has provided us with personal information, we will take steps to delete such information. \n\n
JOB APPLICANTS \n
If you apply for a job at MicroBoss, we collect and use your personal data for legitimate human resources and business management reasons including:
• identifying and evaluating candidates for potential employment, as well as for future roles that may become available. \n\n
•	recordkeeping in relation to recruiting and hiring. \n
•	ensuring compliance with legal requirements, including diversity and inclusion requirements and practices. \n
•	conducting criminal history checks as permitted by applicable law. \n
•	protecting our legal rights to the extent authorized or permitted by law; or
•	emergency situations where the health or safety of one or more individuals may be endangered. \n\n
Your personal data may be accessed by recruiters and interviewers working in the country where the position for which you are applying is based, as well as by recruiters and interviewers working in different countries. \n
We use third party service providers to provide a recruiting software system. We also share your personal data with other third-party service providers that may assist us in recruiting talent, administering, and evaluating pre-employment screening and testing, and improving our recruiting practices. \n\n
RECOURSE AND ENFORCEMENT \n
This section describes how to contact us about our practices or to make a complaint, the complaint and recourse methods available to you, and the enforcement powers to which we are subject. \n
In compliance with our Privacy Policy, MicroBoss commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. Companies and individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Policy or Terms of Service should first contact MicroBoss at: \n\n\n
team@MicroBoss.org or info@MicroBoss.org\n
+234 8056 3333 18 or 08056 3333 19\n
Suite 7, 1st Floor, Right Wing, Z. M. Plaza, Plot 1469, Ahmadu Bello Way, Area 11, Garki 2, Abuja, Nigeria, West Africa. \n\n\n
If you have an unresolved complaint, MicroBoss has committed to an alternative dispute resolution provider located in Nigeria. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not resolved your complaint, please contact us through the email “Complaint@MicroBoss.org” \n\n
UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY \n
MicroBoss may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do update it, for your convenience, we will make the updated Privacy Policy available on this page. Please check this Privacy Policy periodically for changes. If we make any material changes, we will notify you by email (sent to the email address specified in your account registered with the Site or Platform) or by means of a notice on the Site or Platform. \n\n
GLOSSARY \n
I. “Analytics Data” means information about how the Site and/or the Platform are performing. \n
II. “Do Not Track” is a technology and policy proposal that enables users to opt out of tracking by websites they do not visit, including analytics services, advertising networks, and social platforms. \n
III. “Interactive Areas” means the Site’s publicly accessible blogs, community forums, comments sections, discussion forums, training material, event registration or other interactive features. \n
IV.	“MicroBoss”, “we” and “us” mean MicroBoss the Company and all its subsidiaries. \n
V.	“MicroBoss Users” means individuals designated by the MicroBoss customer as a
user of the MicroBoss software products or Platform. \n
VI. “MicroBoss Customers” means companies that license MicroBoss software products or Platform, including “Powered by MicroBoss” and white label versions. \n
VII.	“NAI” means the Network Advertising Initiative. \n
VIII.	“Personal Information” means information that personally identifies and/or locates
you as further described in the Privacy Policy. \n
IX. “Platform” means MicroBoss’s software products, including the MicroBoss stores, solutions, apps, processes, Data Platform, Data Apps, Powered by MicroBoss and white- label deployments. \n
X. “Site” means any website operated and maintained by MicroBoss, a list of which can be reviewed at https://www.officialsites.MicroBoss.org\n
XI. “Usage Data” means information about all of your interactions with the Site and/or the Platform. It may include information regarding any interaction you have with the Site or Platform, such as which functionalities are used and the frequency of use (e.g., pages visited, actions taken, queries run, fields added, user accounts, account roles, and connected database types). \n
</string>
    <string name="confirm_your_reg">You are now reserving a spot for the $SESSION_NAME scheduled for $SESSION_DATE. Details of your reservation will be mail to you shortly...

        \nSee you there!</string>
    <string name="BRONZE_package">Recognized partner \n• Gets brand featured in our event • Share live screen</string>
    <string name="BRONZE_package_full">Sponsor ribbons (on sponsor listing page) on our website and mobile app including banner ads.\n\n
        Agenda Highlights (place their logo or ads in the agenda for high visibility) asides downloadable PDFs of the company profile.
        \n\nLive display (shared screen with other sponsors)</string>

    <string name="SILVER_package">Brand website and product visibility \n• Recognized partner \n• Gets brand featured in our event \n• Share live screen</string>
    <string name="SILVER_package_full">Media exposure on all our global platforms including logo placement in electronic and print adverts and display of company profile including
        corporate name, website url, social media handles and 5 product links listed on our event website and custom app.\n\n
        Sponsor ribbons (on sponsor listing page) on our website and mobile app including banner ads.\n\n
        Agenda Highlights (place their logo or ads in the agenda for high visibility) asides downloadable PDFs of the company profile.\n\n
        Live display (shared screen with other sponsors)</string>

    <string name="GOLD_package">Upgrade to Panelist \n• Brand website and product visibility \n• Recognized partner \n• Gets brand featured in our event \n• Share live screen</string>
    <string name="GOLD_package_full">One full page advert in the CTD event programne and exhibitors guide for 3 consecutive sessions.\n\n
        2 Co-sponsor Access – with upgrade to panelist during one CTD event.\n\nMedia exposure on all our global platforms including logo placement in
        electronic and print adverts and display of company profile including corporate name, website url, social media handles and 5 product links listed on our event website and custom app.\n\n
        Sponsor ribbons (on sponsor listing page) on our website and mobile app including banner ads.\n\n
        Agenda Highlights (place their logo or ads in the agenda for high visibility) asides downloadable PDFs of the company profile.\n\n
        Live display (shared screen with other sponsors)</string>
    <string name="PLATINUM_package">Access to participants\' contacts \n• Upgrade to Panelist \n• Brand website and product visibility \n• Recognized as \'event partner\' \n•
        Gets brand featured in our event • Share live screen</string>
    <string name="PLATINUM_package_full">Recognized as an event partner on all series of Connecting the Dots in the year and her \'Mothership – DNS Out of Africa\'
        Festival event promotional and media kits.\n\nAccess to contact details of participants that indicate willingness to have their personal information shared
        with our key sponsor.\n\nOne full page advert in the CTD event programme and exhibitors guide for 3 consecutive sessions.
        \n\n2 Co-sponsor Access – with upgrade to panelist during one CTD event.\n\nMedia exposure on all our global platforms including logo placement in electronic
        and print adverts and display of company profile including corporate name, website url, social media handles and 5 product links listed on our event website
        and custom app.\n\nSponsor ribbons (on sponsor listing page) on our website and mobile app including banner ads.\n\nAgenda Highlights (place their logo or
        ads in the agenda for high visibility) asides downloadable PDFs of the company profile.\n\nLive display (shared screen with other sponsors)</string>

    <string name="DIAMOND_package">Brand on incentives \n• VIP Access \n• Co-sponsor access \n• Access to participants\' contacts \n• Upgrade to Panelist \n• Brand website and product visibility \n• Recognized as \'event partner\' •
        Gets brand featured in our event • Share live screen</string>
    <string name="DIAMOND_package_full">Brand logo and inserts on CTD\'s visitor/delegates incentives - barges and bags.\n\n8 VIP Access – with upgrade to panelist during one CTD event.
        \n\nRecognized as an event partner on all series of Connecting the Dots in the year and her \'Mothership – DNS Out of Africa\' Festival event promotional and media kits.
        \n\nAccess to contact details of participants that indicate willingness to have their personal information shared with our key sponsor.\n\nOne full page advert in the CTD event programne and exhibitors guide for 3 consecutive sessions.\n\n2 Co-sponsor Access – with upgrade to panelist during one CTD event.
        \n\nMedia exposure on all our global platforms including logo placement in electronic and print adverts and display of company profile including corporate name, website url, social media handles and 5 product links listed on our event website and custom app.\n\nSponsor ribbons (on sponsor listing page) on our website and mobile app including banner ads.\n\nAgenda Highlights (place their logo or ads in the agenda for high visibility) asides downloadable PDFs of the company profile.\n\nLive display (shared screen with other sponsors)</string>

    <string name="title_activity_video_stream">FullscreenActivity</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="naira_symbols">₦</string>
    <string name="pounds_symbols">£</string>
    <string name="euro_symbols">€</string>
    <string name="delete_profile_heading">The following information is your complete data in accord with MicroBoss. This information is not shared and in accordance with the GDPR, using the \'DELETE MY PROFILE\' button below voids this set of data with MicroBoss Technologies. Any adjustments you set here will also be updated on MicroBoss\' storage servers.</string>
</resources>
